Eva's new friend has big eyes, hairy feet, and very sticky fingers.
Monkey Trouble is a comedy, family film directed by Franco Amurri.
Dodger, a criminal monkey, belongs to a crooked street performer but escapes his life of crime only to end up in the
arms of Eva, an innocent little girl whose mother has no idea that her daughter is harboring a fugitive.
Dodger, played by Finster.
Eva, played by Thora Birch.
Azro, played by Harvey Keitel.
Amy, played by Mimi Rogers.
Tom, played by Christopher McDonald.
Jack, played by Adrian Johnson.
Monkey Trouble is a 1994 comedy film directed by Franco Amurri
and starring Thora Birch and Harvey Keitel.
Amurri dedicated the film to his daughter Eva and
named the film's protagonist after her.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship, pet shop, thief, monkey.
The tone is lighthearted.